AV
New York University Archives
- Audiovisual Recordings
  - Women in Careers conference (tape 1 of 3), 25 April 1975; AV2053; Original format: 1/4" audio; Gitlow, Abraham L. (Abraham Leo), 1918-; Leonard N. Stern School of Business. (Box 52, Reel 2053)
  - M. Nadler (College of Business and Public Administration), 1961; AV2100 (Box 54, Reel 2100)
    1/4" open reel original; 3 3/4 speed. Scotch Brand Magnetic Tape (3M)
    Nadler, Marcus, 1895-1965; Taggart, Dr. Joseph H., 1903-1984
  - NYU v. University of Rochester (basketball) (tape 1 of 2), 1989 January 20; AV2146 (Box 55, Item 2146)
    Sony broadcast standard videocassette
    This material is related to RG 41.1, Records of the Basketball Program, Department of Athletics. Tape C00557.
  - NYU v. University of Rochester (basketball) (tape 2 of 2), 1989 January 20; AV2147 (Box 55, Item 2147)
    This material is related to RG 41.1, Records of the Basketball Program, Department of Athletics. Tape C00558.
  - NYU v. University of Rochester (basketball) (tape 1 of 3), 1988 January 30; AV2148 (Box 55, Item 2148)
    This material is related to RG 41.1, Records of the Basketball Program, Department of Athletics.
  - NYU v. University of Rochester (basketball) (tape 2 of 3), 1988 January 30; AV2149 (Box 55, Item 2149)
  - NYU v. University of Rochester (basketball) (tape 3 of 3), 1988 January 30; AV2150 (Box 55, Item 2150)
  - NYU v. Emory University (basketball) (tape 1 of 3), 1988 January 15; AV2155 (Box 55, Item 2155)
  - NYU v. Emory University (basketball) (tape 2 of 3), 1988 January 15; AV2156 (Box 55, Item 2156)
  - NYU v. Emory University (basketball) (tape 3 of 3), 1988 January 15; AV2157 (Box 56, Item 2157)
    Sony broadcast standard cassette
  - NYU v. City College of New York (basketball) (tape 1 of 2), 1988 January 7; AV2158 (Box 56, Item 2158)
  - NYU v. City College of New York (basketball) (tape 2 of 2), 1988 January 7; AV2159 (Box 56, Item 2159)
  - NYU v. College of Staten Island (basketball) (tape 3 of 3), 1986 December 20; AV2160 (Box 56, Item 2160)
  - NYU v. Vassar College (basketball) (tape 1 of 3), 1988 December 5; AV2161 (Box 56, Item 2161)
    Ampex 197 BCA broadcast videocassette
    This material is related to RG 41.1, Records of the Basketball Program, Department of Athletics. Tape C00347.
  - NYU v. Vassar College (basketball) (tape 2 of 3), 1988 December 5; AV2162 (Box 56, Item 2162)
    This material is related to RG 41.1, Records of the Basketball Program, Department of Athletics. Tape C00348.
  - NYU v. Vassar College (basketball) (tape 3 of 3), 1988 December 5; AV2163 (Box 56, Item 2163)
    This material is related to RG 41.1, Records of the Basketball Program, Department of Athletics. Tape C00349.
  - NYU v. Catholic University of America (basketball) (tape 1 of 3), 1985 December 16; AV2164 (Box 56, Item 2164)
    Fuji KCA-60 Beriodov videocassette
  - NYU v. Catholic University of America (basketball) (tape 2 of 3), 1985 December 16; AV2165 (Box 56, Item 2165)
    Technical access
    Sony KCA broadcast standard videocassette
  - Inauguration: L. Jay Oliva (1 of 2), 21 November 1991; AV2193 (Box 57, Item 2193)
    Digital surrogates
    This tape has been digitized, and an access copy resides at the Archives.
    Oliva, Lawrence Jay, 1933-
  - Inauguration: L. Jay Oliva (2 of 2), 21 Nov. 1991 (Box 57, Item 2194)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2215 (Box 57, Item 2215)
    This tape is related to materials in RG 3.0.10, Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas).
    3/4" location tapes; 30 min. Sony KCA-30 BRK
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2216 (Box 57, Item 2216)
    3/4" location tapes; 30 min. Sony KCA-30 BRS
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2217 (Box 57, Item 2217)
    3/4" location tapes, 30 min. Sony KCA-30 BRS
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra and other villa, 1987 July 30; AV2218 (Box 57, Item 2218)
    3/4" location tapes, 30 min. Sony KCA-30 BRK
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, grape orchard, 1987 July 30; AV2219 (Box 57, Item 2219)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, interview with Acton at the temple, 1987 July 30; AV2220 (Box 57, Item 2220)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, Lemon garden pasquilina, Dr. Brademas asking questions, 1987 July 30; AV2221 (Box 57, Item 2221)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, conversations between Acton and Dr. Brademas, 1987 July 30; AV2222 (Box 57, Item 2222)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, conversations between Acton and Dr. Brademas, AV2223 (Box 58, Item 2223)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2224 (Box 58, Item 2224)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2225 (Box 58, Item 2225)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2226 (Box 58, Item 2226)
    3/4 " location tapes; 30 min. Sony KCA-30 BRS
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, Dr. Brademas' questions and reaction shots, 1987 July 30; AV2227 (Box 58, Item 2227)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, views of Duomo from garden of main house of Sassetti, 1987 July 30; AV2228 (Box 58, Item 2228)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, view from V. Olivi open theater, 1987 July 30; AV2229 (Box 58, Item 2229)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, conversations with Acton and Dr. Brademas, 1987 July 30; AV2230 (Box 58, Item 2230)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2231 (Box 58, Item 2231)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, conversations with Acton and Dr. Brademas, 1987 July 30; AV2232 (Box 58, Item 2232)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, Dr. Brademas' questions, 1987 July 30; AV2233 (Box 58, Item 2233)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2234 (Box 58, Item 2234)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, Ponte Vecchio, Museo Horne, 1987 July 30; AV2235 (Box 58, Item 2235)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, I Tatti, Professor Clubb, 1987 July 30; AV2236 (Box 58, Item 2236)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, Piazza Signoria Della, 1987 July 30; AV2237 (Box 58, Item 2237)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, stills of photographs, views from hall into garden, 1987 July 30; AV2238 (Box 59, Item 2238)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, stills (B)-China Pix-Old Villa P. Pix, 1987 July 30; AV2239 (Box 59, Item 2239)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, stills (C)-old villa before Italian garden, 1987 July 30; AV2240 (Box 59, Item 2240)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, conversation with Acton on Cina and his house, 1987 July 30; AV2241 (Box 59, Item 2241)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, views of Cypress Avenue, 1987 July 30; AV2242 (Box 59, Item 2242)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, interiors, red damask room, "Rape of the Sabinets" above staircase, 1987 July 30; AV2243 (Box 59, Item 2243)
    3/4" Location tapes; 30 min. Sony KCA-30 BRS
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, grotto room, 1987 July 30; AV2244 (Box 59, Item 2244)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2245 (Box 59, Item 2245)
    Related material
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2246 (Box 59, Item 2246)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2247 (Box 59, Item 2247)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2248 (Box 59, Item 2248)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, art on second floor (Madonna in bedroom), Acton in his study, dog, 1987 July 30; AV2249 (Box 59, Item 2249)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, Acton and Carter Brown, 1987 July 30; AV2250 (Box 59, Item 2250)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, conversations with Acton and Carter Brown, 1987 July 30; AV2251 (Box 59, Item 2251)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, conversations facing Carter Brown, 1987 July 30; AV2252 (Box 59, Item 2252)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, stills (aquarium, Oxford bedroom, front gate from inside villa), 1987 July 30; AV2253 (Box 59, Item 2253)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, questions (Carter Brown), 1987 July 30; AV2254 (Box 60, Item 2254)
    3/4" location tape; 30 min. Sony KCA-30 BRK
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2255 (Box 60, Item 2255)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2256 (Box 60, Item 2256)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2257 (Box 60, Item 2257)
  - Harold Acton Tape Project: La Pietra, 1987 July 30; AV2258 (Box 60, Item 2258)
  - 100th Anniversary of the School of Engineering and Science, 1955; AV2283 (Box 60, Reel 2283)
  - 100th Anniversary of the School of Engineering and Science, 1955; AV2284 (Box 60, Reel 2284)
  - 100th Anniversary of the School of Engineering and Science, 1955; AV2285 (Box 61, Reel 2285)
  - 100th Anniversary of the School of Engineering and Science, 1955; AV2286 (Box 61, Reel 2286)
  - 100th Anniversary of the School of Engineering and Science, 1955; AV2288 (Box 61, Reel 2288)
  - 100th Anniversary of the School of Engineering and Science, 1955; AV2287 (Box 61, Reel 2287)
  - 100th Anniversary of the School of Engineering and Science, 1955; AV2289 (Box 61, Reel 2289)
  - Commencement Exercises (tape 1 of 2), 1966 June 8; AV2306; Goldberg, Arthur J. (Box 61, Disc 2306, Reel 2306)
    Original format: 1/4" audio, Scotch, 1.5 mil acetate, 7" reel
  - Commencement Exercises (tape 2 of 2), 1966 June 8; AV2307 (Box 61, Disc 2307, Box 123, Reel 2307)
    The speaker on this reel of the 1966 commencement exercises was George A. Murphy.
  - "Our Happiest Birthday", 1976 July 4; AV2561; Cronkite, Walter (Box 66, Cassette 2561)
    Original format: U-matic
  - The City and the University, undated; AV2940 (Box 78, Reel 2940)
    Original format: 16 mm composite b/w print
    This item has not yet been digitized.
    A label on the original can reads: "Allegro Film Productions, Inc. 201 West 52nd Street, New York N.Y. 10019, JUdson 6-3057/Documentaries, Print Procurement, Industrials, Commercials, News Films, Sports Films, Lab Liason)
  - NYU Commencements, 1953-1966; AV2948 (Box 123, Disc 2948, Box 78, Reel 2948)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    This item is 8mm film and has been digitized. Please contact the repository for access information.
  - NYU v. Hobart College (football), 1932; AV2949 (Box 78, Reel 2949)
    This material is related to RG 41.4, Records of the Football Program, Department of Athletics.
    Original format: 16mm film
    Football.; New York University |x Athletics.
  - NYU v. unknown opponent (basketball), undated; AV2954 (Reel AV2954)
    Original format: 16mm film, reversal, safety acetate, Kodak 51 safety stock, b&w, silent, 3 cement splices (1 repaired with tape), 1.5% shrinkage, level 3 on IPI scale, no original leader, inspection done in preservation lab 2/5/2010
    Basketball.; New York University |x Athletics.
  - NYU v. Villanova University (football), 1930; AV2966 (Box 79, Reel 2966)
  - NYU v. Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey (football), 1930; AV2971 (Box 80, Reel 2971)
  - NYU v. Pennsylvania State University (football), 1929; AV2973 (Box 80, Reel 2973)
  - NYU v. Georgetown University (football), 1932; AV2974 (Box 80, Reel 2974)
    Original format 16mm film.
    Related materials at the New York University Archives
  - NYU v. West Virginia Wesleyan University (football), 13 October 1934; AV2991 (Box 80, Reel 2991)
    Original format: 16mm film, positive, b&w, acetate, 300 ft, mild wear, some smudging on base, 0.5% shrinkage, silent
    Contents
    Original packaging labeled #10 Football.
  - NYU v. Pennsylvania State University (football), 19 October 1929; AV2992 (Box 81, Reel 2992)
    Original packaging read: NI-11
    Football.; New York University |x Athletics.; Yankee Stadium (New York, N.Y.: 1923-2009)
  - Dinner and Presentation of the New York University Gallatin Medal to Richard Courant, 1967; AV3016; 2.0 sound discs (vinyl); Label on container: "Impressions in Sound by Phonotone." Each disc labeled: "Phonotone Recording Company."; Gallatin Associates. (Box 83, Item 3016)
    Playback speed: 33 1/3 RPM.
    This recording is related to materials in RG 37.18, Records of the Albert Gallatin Associates, RG 46.8, Records of the Presentation of University Awards, and MC 150, the Richard Courant Papers.
    Courant, Richard, 1888-1972; Mathematics.
  - Interview with President Oliva (tape 1 of 4), 8 August 1995; AV3113; Original format: VHS; Oliva, Lawrence Jay, 1933- (Box 86, Cassette 3113)
    This material is related to RG 6.0.8, Records of the Office of the Chancellor and/or Executive Vice President (Oliva) and RG 3.0.11, Records of the Office of the President (Oliva).
  - Interview with President Oliva (tape 2 of 4), 8 August 1995; AV3114; Original format: VHS; Oliva, Lawrence Jay, 1933- (Box 86, Cassette 3114)
  - Interview with President Oliva (tape 3 of 4), 8 August 1995; AV3115; Original format: VHS; Oliva, Lawrence Jay, 1933- (Box 86, Cassette 3115)
  - Interview with President Oliva (tape 4 of 4), 8 August 1995; AV3116; Original format: VHS; Oliva, Lawrence Jay, 1933- (Box 86, Cassette 3116)
  - The Miracle at Washington Square, undated; AV3145 (Box 87, Item 3145)
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (final lecture) (tape 1 of 9), 19 December 1963A; AV3147; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3147)
    Original format: 1/4" open reel Original stock: Scotch 1.5 mil acetate, 7" reel Barcode: 31142046549534
    The University Archives does not have tapes representing lectures 1, 6, and 7 in this series.
    Titian, ca. 1488-1576
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture 11) (tape 2 of 9), 12 December 1963; AV3148; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3148)
    Original format: 1/4" open reel Original stock: Scotch 1.5 mil acetate, 7" reel
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture 10) (tape 3 of 9), 15 December [1963]; AV3149; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3149)
    Original format: 1/4" open reel Original stock: Scotch 1.5 mil acetate, 7" reel barcode: 31142046549526
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture 9) (tape 4 of 9), 1963 November 14; AV3150; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3150)
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture 8) (tape 5 of 9), [1963]; AV3151; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3151)
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture V) (tape 6 of 9), [1963]; AV3152 (Box 87, Reel 3152)
    Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968; Titian, ca. 1488-1576
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture IV) (tape 7 of 9), [1963]; AV3153 (Box 87, Reel 3153)
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture 3) (tape 8 of 9), [1963]; AV3154; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3154)
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture II, Tape 9 of 9), [1963]; AV3155; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3155)
  - MacNeil/Lehrer Newshour: Galway, AV3272; Brademas, John, 1927- (Box 90, Item 3272)
  - Today Show, AV3273; Brademas, John, 1927- (Box 90, Item 3273)
  - First-year report on $100 million fundraising drive, AV3274; Brademas, John, 1927- (Box 90, Item 3274)
  - New Day Chicago (WBBM-TV): "Dr. Brademas, President of NYU", AV3275; Brademas, John, 1927- (Box 90, Item 3275)
  - Face the Nation (CBS-TV), AV3276 (Box 90, Item 3276)
  - Modern Maturity, AV3278; Brademas, John, 1927- (Box 90, Item 3278)
  - CBS Sunday Morning News, undated; AV3279; Brademas, John, 1927- (Box 90, Item 3279)
  - The Open Mind, undated; AV3280; Brademas, John, 1927- (Box 90, Item 3280)
    Richard Heffner and Jan Waldman also appear in this tape.
  - Larry Tisch Buys 25% of CBS (CBS-TV), AV3281; Brademas, John, 1927- (Box 90, Item 3281)
  - Today Show (NBC-TV), undated; AV3282; Brademas, John, 1927- (Box 90, Item 3282)
  - "L. Jay Oliva College Athletics" on Morning Program, CBS TV (tape 1 of 3), 7 March 2001; AV3283; Original format: VHS; Oliva, Lawrence Jay, 1933- (Box 90, Cassette 3283)
    College sports.; New York University |x Athletics.
  - "L. Jay Oliva College Athletics" on Morning Program, CBS TV (tape 2 of 3), 7 March 2001; AV3284; Original format: VHS; Oliva, Lawrence Jay, 1933- (Box 90, Cassette 3284)
  - "L. Jay Oliva College Athletics" on Morning Program, CBS TV (tape 3 of 3), 7 March 2001; AV3285; Original format: VHS; Oliva, Lawrence Jay, 1933- (Box 90, Cassette 3285)
  - Dedication of the K.V. Weissman Clinical Science Building, NYU College of Dentistry, Part 1, 1961 January 21; AV3394; New York University. College of Dentistry. (Box 93, Reel 3394)
    1/4" open reel original; Speed 7 1/2; Scotch Magentic Tape (3M).
  - Dedication of the K.V. Weissman Clinical Science Building, NYU College of Dentistry, Part 2, 1961 January 21; AV3395; New York University. College of Dentistry. (Box 93, Reel 3395)
  - NYU College of Dentistry: Centennial celebration, dedication of plaque, 1965 January 27; AV3397 (Box 93, Item 3397)
    This tape is related to materials in RG 25, Records of the New York University College of Dentistry.
  - "NYU Tonight" profile of L. Jay Oliva, 26 April 2001; AV3426; Original format: VHS (Box 94, Cassette 3426)
  - "The Open Mind" with Dr. L. Jay Oliva, 2 October 1996; AV3444; Original format: VHS (Box 94, Cassette 3444)
  - Voices of the Encounter (tapes 1 and 2), undated; AV3483 (Box 95, Item 3483)
    This tape is related to materials in RG 9.5.1, Records of the Humanities Council.
  - God's Trombones (tapes 1 and 2), undated; AV3491 (Box 96, Item 3491)
  - Voices of the Encounter (the Columbus legacy), AV3520; Berzins, Zane (Box 97, Item 3520)
  - Martin Cherlasky Lecture (tape 2 of 3 and tape 3 of 3), undated; AV3603 (Box 99, Item 3603)
    Dr. David Kessler lectured at this event.
    This tape is related to materials in RG 33, Records of the Robert F. Wagner School of Public Service.
  - "Dr. L. Jay Oliva/NYU" on Fox on Education, 18 December 1996; AV3858; This material is related to RG 6.0.8, Records of the Office of the Chancellor and/or Executive Vice President (Oliva) and RG 3.0.11, Records of the Office of the President (Oliva). (Box 106, Cassette 3858)
  - New York 1 news broadcast about L. Jay Oliva (2 tapes), undated; AV3875; Original format: VHS; NY1. (Box 106, Cassette 3875)
    Copyright information
    This program was originally broadcast on NY1's "Hourly News" program and rights to the content may reside with that network.
  - Federal Energy Office: U.S. Energy Policy and You, AV3877; Sawhill, John C., 1936- (Box 107, Item 3877)
  - Lou Dobbs interview with L. Jay Oliva (2 tapes), 1 February 1997; AV3891; Original format: VHS; Dobbs, Lou (Box 107, Cassette AV3891)
    This program was originally broadcast on CNN and rights to the content may reside with that network.
  - NYU Lewis L. and Loretta Brennan Ireland House Dedication, 1993 April 26; AV3919 (Box 107, Cassette 3919)
    Original format: VHS, TDK HS
    Ireland House.
  - New York University: The One Hundred Fifty-ninth Commencement Exercises, 1991 May 16; AV3925; Guarino, Elisa; New York University. (Box 108, Cassette 3925)
    Copies available
    Digitized copy available. Please ask at Archives.
    New York University. Office of Public Affairs.
  - Inauguration of L. Jay Oliva, 21 November 1991; AV3929; Original format: VHS (Box 108, Cassette 3929)
  - NYU Lewis L. and Loretta Brennan Ireland House Dedication, 1993 April 26; AV3934 (Box 108, Cassette 3934)
    Original format: VHS, T-120, Scotch 3M EG
  - Recruitment: David B. Kriser Center, undated; AV3968 (Box 110, Item 3968)
  - NYU football, undated; AV2913; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 2,913)
    Related Materials
    This item is related to RG41, records of the Department of Athletics
  - Berlin Olympics 1936, AV2914; Original Format: 16 mm film; Original Film is (Box 77, Reel 2,914)
    This material is related to RG 41, Records of the Department of Athletics
    Olympics.
  - NYU vs. unknown opponent (football) (11), AV2915; Original Film is B&W, Silent; Original Format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel 2,915)
    This item is related to RG 41, records of the Department of Athletics
  - NYU vs. unknown opponent (football) (17), AV2916; Original Format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel 2,917)
  - NYU vs. unknown opponent (NI-10), AV2917; Original film is: B&W, Silent; Original Format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel 2,917)
    Football.; New York University. NYU Press.
  - NYU vs. St. Louis, 1952; AV2918; Original Format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,918)
  - NYU vs Dartmouth, 1950; AV2919; Original Format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,919)
  - NYU vs Carnegie Mellon, 1936; AV2920; Original format: 16mm film (Box 77, Reel 2,920)
    New York University |x Athletics.
  - NYU vs Illinois, 1964; AV2921; Original format: 8 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,920)
    This item is related to RG 41, the records of the Department of Athletics
    Basketball.; New York University. NYU Press.
  - NYU vs Dartmouth, 1949; AV2922; Original format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,922)
  - NYU vs Notre Dame, 1950; AV2923; Original format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,923)
    This item relates to RG 41, records of the Department of Athletics
  - NYU vs North Carolina, 1949; AV2924; Original format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Box Reel 2,924)
  - NYU vs. St Louis, 1952; AV2925; Original format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,925)
  - NYU vs LaSalle College, 1961; AV2926; Original format: 8 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,926)
  - NYU vs. Colgate, 1950; AV2927; Original format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,927)
  - NYU vs Notre Dame, 1951 February 26; AV2928; Original format: 16mm film (Box 77, Reel 2,928)
  - NYU vs. Notre Dame, 1951; AV2928; Original format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,928)
  - NYU vs St. Louis, 1952; AV2929; Original format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,929)
    This item related to RG 41, records of the Department of Athletics
  - NYU vs Notre Dame, 1951 February 26; AV2930; Original format: 16mm film (Box 77, Reel 2,930)
  - NYU vs. North Carolina, 1946; AV2931; Original format: 16mm film (Box 77, Reel 2,931)
    This item related to RG41, records of the Department of Athletics
  - NYU vs. Yale (JV), 1964; AV2932; Original format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,932)
  - NYU vs. Yale (JV), 1964; AV2933; Original format: 16 mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,933)
  - NYU vs Brigham Young, 1966; AV2934; Original format: 16mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,934)
  - NYU vs. SMU, 1946-1947; AV2935; Original format: 16mm film (Box 77, Reel Reel 2,935)
  - NYU vs. University of North Carolina (Reel 1), 1949; AV2936; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,936)
    This item is related to RG 41.4, Records of the Football Program, Department of Athletics.
  - NYU vs. University of Texas (Reel 3), 1948; AV2937; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,937)
  - NYU vs. University of North Carolina (Reel 3), 1949; AV2938; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,938)
  - Yale vs NYU (Reel 1), 1948; AV2939; Original format: 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,939)
  - NYU vs Fordham (Reel 3), 1948; AV2941; Original format: 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,941)
  - Jamestown (2 of 4), unknown; AV2942; Original format: 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,942)
  - Jamestown (1 of 4), unknown; AV2943; Original format: 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,943)
  - NYU vs. Fordham (Reel 2), 1948; AV2944; Original format: 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,944)
  - NYU vs. Fordham (Reel 1), 1948; AV2945; Original format: 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,945)
  - Hobart vs. VA Wesleyan, 1930; AV2946; Original format: 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,946)
  - NYU vs. Georgetown, 1948; AV2947; Original format: 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,947)
  - NYU Commencement, unknown; AV2948; Original format: 8mm film (Box 78, Reel 2,948)